[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "Was it emotional?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "emotional", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "Oh, very.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "very", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Am I allowed to call you Todd?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "allowed", "to", "call", "you", "Todd", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "You should -- you're definitely allowed to call me Todd.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "should", "--", "you", "'re", "definitely", "allowed", "to", "call", "me", "Todd", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "When you heard what has happened, what was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "heard", "what", "has", "happened", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, you know, my first reaction was -- it was horrifying, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "my", "first", "reaction", "was", "--", "it", "was", "horrifying", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Did you know Whitney well?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "Whitney", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Yes, I knew Whitney.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "knew", "Whitney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "What gave you that idea to do that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "gave", "you", "that", "idea", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "You know, I -- I was thinking about it and it was the only way that I felt -- I would feel comfortable proceeding with the show and celebrating all of these other musicians, because it was about trying to find that fine balance between celebrating her legacy, giving love to this wonderful, amazing entertainer, and, at the same time, respecting all of these young artists and all of these established artists who were either nominated for Grammys or performing on the show and not putting them in the position where they have to perform at a memorial.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "--", "I", "was", "thinking", "about", "it", "and", "it", "was", "the", "only", "way", "that", "I", "felt", "--", "I", "would", "feel", "comfortable", "proceeding", "with", "the", "show", "and", "celebrating", "all", "of", "these", "other", "musicians", ",", "because", "it", "was", "about", "trying", "to", "find", "that", "fine", "balance", "between", "celebrating", "her", "legacy", ",", "giving", "love", "to", "this", "wonderful", ",", "amazing", "entertainer", ",", "and", ",", "at", "the", "same", "time", ",", "respecting", "all", "of", "these", "young", "artists", "and", "all", "of", "these", "established", "artists", "who", "were", "either", "nominated", "for", "Grammys", "or", "performing", "on", "the", "show", "and", "not", "putting", "them", "in", "the", "position", "where", "they", "have", "to", "perform", "at", "a", "memorial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Do you understand the particular pressure, as a former -- that led her to enter that spiral of self-abuse towards the end?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "the", "particular", "pressure", ",", "as", "a", "former", "--", "that", "led", "her", "to", "enter", "that", "spiral", "of", "self-abuse", "towards", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "IN", "JJ", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Of course I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Was music always your first love?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "music", "always", "your", "first", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well -- well, yes, you drift away.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--", "well", ",", "yes", ",", "you", "drift", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBG", "PRP"], "qSentId": 343, "question": "What is it to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Whatever goal I'm going -- I want to achieve, achieving it", "answer_tokens": ["Whatever", "goal", "I", "'m", "going", "--", "I", "want", "to", "achieve", ",", "achieving", "it"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Oh, God, I don't even want to think about that, right?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "God", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "even", "want", "to", "think", "about", "that", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "I'm not saying it's going to happen imminently.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "saying", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "happen", "imminently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "But, you know, things -- all being relative and everything being even, it's what you don't do that you'll ultimately regret, you know?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "you", "know", ",", "things", "--", "all", "being", "relative", "and", "everything", "being", "even", ",", "it", "'s", "what", "you", "do", "n't", "do", "that", "you", "'ll", "ultimately", "regret", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ":", "DT", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Well, you're doing a hell of a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'re", "doing", "a", "hell", "of", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "My Connect Studio is available now?", "question_tokens": ["My", "Connect", "Studio", "is", "available", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "When is the new album out?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "the", "new", "album", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "You know what, I'm working on it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", ",", "I", "'m", "working", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Is she here?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Ann Marie, what did you do?", "question_tokens": ["Ann", "Marie", ",", "what", "did", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Well you said to keep him busy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "you", "said", "to", "keep", "him", "busy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ann Marie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Do you get sick of the degrees of separation?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "sick", "of", "the", "degrees", "of", "separation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Did you know she was the one?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "she", "was", "the", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Do you remember the first time you met him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "the", "first", "time", "you", "met", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Is it luck and just finding the right person?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "luck", "and", "just", "finding", "the", "right", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "I mean, do you have a certain way that you are with each other that just works?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "have", "a", "certain", "way", "that", "you", "are", "with", "each", "other", "that", "just", "works", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "You know, I think we did just get lucky, but I also think that we have the same priorities and I think that helps a lot because we know that our relationship has to be sort of the primary relationship and the primary purpose of our lives in a way, even though we have so many other parts of our lives that are important.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "we", "did", "just", "get", "lucky", ",", "but", "I", "also", "think", "that", "we", "have", "the", "same", "priorities", "and", "I", "think", "that", "helps", "a", "lot", "because", "we", "know", "that", "our", "relationship", "has", "to", "be", "sort", "of", "the", "primary", "relationship", "and", "the", "primary", "purpose", "of", "our", "lives", "in", "a", "way", ",", "even", "though", "we", "have", "so", "many", "other", "parts", "of", "our", "lives", "that", "are", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What was it like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "It was -- it was scary.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "--", "it", "was", "scary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "How old are they now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "are", "they", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "They are -- my son is about to turn 23 and my daughter is 20.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "--", "my", "son", "is", "about", "to", "turn", "23", "and", "my", "daughter", "is", "20", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Do they find it hard being the products of two famous acting stars?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "find", "it", "hard", "being", "the", "products", "of", "two", "famous", "acting", "stars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I don't think they know any better.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "they", "know", "any", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "It slightly blurs the line, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "slightly", "blurs", "the", "line", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Will you dance with me?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "dance", "with", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "How do you stay so ridiculously youthful?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "stay", "so", "ridiculously", "youthful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "I drink a lot of water.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "drink", "a", "lot", "of", "water", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "How do you get to look like this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "to", "look", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Not ten hours a day, but I do like to exercise.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "ten", "hours", "a", "day", ",", "but", "I", "do", "like", "to", "exercise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "It is quite weird, actually, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "quite", "weird", ",", "actually", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "No, I don't think it is weird.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "is", "weird", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Is that the secret?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "secret", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "No, I think I could have better bone structure.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "I", "could", "have", "better", "bone", "structure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Is that still a topic of interest?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "still", "a", "topic", "of", "interest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Yes, make this quick and brutal.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "make", "this", "quick", "and", "brutal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Can you say that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "So a gun with one bullet, walking down the street, you wouldn't --", "answer_tokens": ["So", "a", "gun", "with", "one", "bullet", ",", "walking", "down", "the", "street", ",", "you", "would", "n't", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Are you an Obama fan generally?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "an", "Obama", "fan", "generally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "I love Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Are you one of these people that I'm going to go and vote?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "one", "of", "these", "people", "that", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "go", "and", "vote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "You feel strongly?", "question_tokens": ["You", "feel", "strongly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Absolutely, 100 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "100", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Are you worried that the Republicans will get in?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "worried", "that", "the", "Republicans", "will", "get", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Always.", "answer_tokens": ["Always", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "What do you think of Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "I need to learn more about him, I think.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "need", "to", "learn", "more", "about", "him", ",", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "What is your gut feeling?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "gut", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "You know, I will be voting for Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "will", "be", "voting", "for", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "You're very diplomatic, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "very", "diplomatic", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "I try to be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "try", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "Do you like Twitter?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "Twitter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "I'm not as good at it -- I'm not as diligent about it as I should be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "as", "good", "at", "it", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "as", "diligent", "about", "it", "as", "I", "should", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Or is it -- for any artist, is it sort of vaguely terrifying as well?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "--", "for", "any", "artist", ",", "is", "it", "sort", "of", "vaguely", "terrifying", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "It is vaguely terrifying, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "vaguely", "terrifying", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "amazing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["December"]}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "How do you feel about this being the end?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "this", "being", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "Well, it has been the end since December.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "has", "been", "the", "end", "since", "December", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Was it emotional?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "emotional", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "EDGWICK: Oh, very.", "answer_tokens": ["EDGWICK", ":", "Oh", ",", "very", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "What are you doing now with all your free time?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "doing", "now", "with", "all", "your", "free", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "Yeah, well, I'm seeing a lot of plays.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "well", ",", "I", "'m", "seeing", "a", "lot", "of", "plays", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Newman"]}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 730, "question": "What has been the best moment of your career, the moment if I could replay it for you right now, you would choose?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "been", "the", "best", "moment", "of", "your", "career", ",", "the", "moment", "if", "I", "could", "replay", "it", "for", "you", "right", "now", ",", "you", "would", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "I think the best -- one of the best moments of my career was working with Paul Newman in \"Mr. and Mrs. Bridge.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "best", "--", "one", "of", "the", "best", "moments", "of", "my", "career", "was", "working", "with", "Paul", "Newman", "in", "``", "Mr.", "and", "Mrs.", "Bridge", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Travis"]}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 745, "question": "What was his advice about kids?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "his", "advice", "about", "kids", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "His advice about kids was -- I remember he looked at me -- I had -- Travis was two months old when I did \"Mr. and Mrs. Bridge.\"", "answer_tokens": ["His", "advice", "about", "kids", "was", "--", "I", "remember", "he", "looked", "at", "me", "--", "I", "had", "--", "Travis", "was", "two", "months", "old", "when", "I", "did", "``", "Mr.", "and", "Mrs.", "Bridge", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "Do you have a big ambition, a particular project or something that you would really love to do?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "big", "ambition", ",", "a", "particular", "project", "or", "something", "that", "you", "would", "really", "love", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "My big ambition is to work in film with great directors.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "big", "ambition", "is", "to", "work", "in", "film", "with", "great", "directors", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Who is the number one?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "the", "number", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "Alexander Pain.", "answer_tokens": ["Alexander", "Pain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ":", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "Why him?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "I think every movie he makes is so other, so brilliant and so spontaneous, and so real and so -- and the characters.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "every", "movie", "he", "makes", "is", "so", "other", ",", "so", "brilliant", "and", "so", "spontaneous", ",", "and", "so", "real", "and", "so", "--", "and", "the", "characters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 765, "question": "Have you had any conversations?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "any", "conversations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 766, "answer": "We've -- I've met him several times and auditioned for him several times.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "--", "I", "'ve", "met", "him", "several", "times", "and", "auditioned", "for", "him", "several", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "He's rejected you?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "rejected", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "Yes, a few times, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "a", "few", "times", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "What was he thinking?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "Is that the dream ticket?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "dream", "ticket", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "Kind of.", "answer_tokens": ["Kind", "of", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "Can you imagine that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "imagine", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "Yes, that would be amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "would", "be", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kev"]}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 785, "question": "What if you both won Oscars on the same year?", "question_tokens": ["What", "if", "you", "both", "won", "Oscars", "on", "the", "same", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "I always say to Kev, where is my \"Dead Man Walking.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "always", "say", "to", "Kev", ",", "where", "is", "my", "``", "Dead", "Man", "Walking", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120706pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 823, "question": "Will you please, please marry me?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "please", ",", "please", "marry", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 824, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]